back. I see him back up here,
>> man.
>> Let me get right.
>> Why did it work so well for you guys
today?
>> I mean, you know, we we had a great game
plan laid out and I think we went out
there and executed, you know, we played
complimentary football. Um, we put the
offense up where they need us and they
and they made sure they had our back,
too. So,
>> did your game plan make a difference?
>> No, I mean, n like I said, when we had a
game plan out, you know what you're
going to do. You know how you're going
to execute it, man. You just got to go
out there and play ball, man. That's
what makes us who we are. So we we trust
each other. We go out there, do our
thing.
>> Ernest Ernest said that they said you're
a walking Hall of Famer, obviously been
in the league for three seasons, but
what does that mean coming from him? And
what is your confidence level when you
view yourself?
>> I mean, it mean a lot. Um, you know, it
means everything, man. He talking about
a great teammate, Ernest, man. He
everything to us, man. He talking about
a might linebacker who set the standard
for us, who go out there and keep us
controlled, keep us composed out there.
I mean, he's everything, you know. Um,
and for that, you know, right now, I'm
really just focused on it now, you know,
living in the present. I'm not really
worried about what everybody else got
going on. Um, I'm just living in the
present right now. So,
>> how much do you enjoy those bliss?
>> I mean, I enjoyed them a lot. You know,
I haven't been blissing a lot this year.
Um, but like I said, it was for the best
of our team. So, I'm going to do
whatever our team need to do to win.
>> Hey, Devin, for this defense, as good as
you've been all year, to have this type
of performance in this moment, what does
it say?
>> Um,
>> it say we handled our business the way
we do all year. Um, like I said, man,
talking about a group of guys who play
together out there, who don't who give
each other everything they need, who
have each other back out there, don't
let another person down. I mean, it's
everything you want in a defense. So,
>> how do you defense is one of the best
defenses in all time of all time?
>> Um, I don't know. I ain't really think
about that. I know we was the best
defense this year and that's all that
matter.
>> How's the rushing coverage out today?
Let's talk about that.
>> I mean, it worked out pretty well. You
talking about we had a great game plan.
We went out there, we rushed for one. We
was able to container most of the game.
Shout out to the D line for doing their
thing and we held our end in the back
end, man. Like I said, we kind of knew
what they was going to do, how they was
going to attack us and how they was
going to get feature, who and certain
people the ball. So, we had a great game
plan like that.
>> Leonard said at you guys thinking shut
out.
>> Yeah, that's never been done in the
Super Bowl.
>> Yeah. How much were you aware of that?
>> I mean, we was aware. Um, like I said,
we kind of let off the gas a little bit
and we like I said, we're going to go
back and watch the film about it. Um,
cuz you set a standard for yourself.
You're going to hold each other to that
standard. Um, we was kind of mad we gave
him two touchdowns at the end of the
game, but you know, they went out there
and earned it though. But, um, it's all
right, man. You know, we we played a
hell of a game tonight. So,
>> when you hit and
you celebrated, what was that moment
like for you?
>> I ain't even know he fumbled the ball to
be honest. Um, it was kind of crazy. My
reaction was kind of late. Um, but it
was I'm just living in the moment. Like
I said, man, I don't think about nothing
crazy or what I'm going to do. I just
live in the moment. So whatever the
reaction was, it was just whatever it
was.
>> Yeah, it's going to be crazy, man. It's
going down in history. So
>> talk to us about the blitz success you
had this week. Is that something you
picked up on as a potential weakness in
their offense?
>> Um yes, like I said, we we kind of knew
how they tackles and guards was going to
set in certain um pass protections and
we we went out there and attacked it. Um
you know, they they they was kind of
struggling in in his playoffs a couple
of times. you know, a couple people got
after him, so we knew what we was going
to do and how we were going to attack
him. But, you know, things happen, man.
It's football in the game. So,
>> are you natural? That's serious. That's
something
you do defensively.
>> I mean, no. Whatever my coach need me to
do, I go out there and do it. So, I
don't really, you look forward to one
thing or the other. I just go out there
and handle business. So,
>> you haven't blissed that much though in
the game.
>> Yes, I bliss a lot in the game before.
So,
>> why do you think you specifically?
>> Um, you know, um, our game plan really
wasn't around him tonight. It was really
more about the quarterback and keeping
him contained in the pocket. And I think
we did a great job with that. Obviously,
you know, he's a great player. You know,
he did a lot of great things in his
league, man. I mean, you look at the guy
body of work, man. You can't you can't
take that from him. So, um I think we
had a great game plan. We just went out
there and executed it.
>> The huddle when you line up and you hear
that it's called what's your mind?
>> Um you know, my keys um when he getting
ready to snap the ball and just hammer a
blitz. So, just just the normal things a
football player do.
>> What's the key to ladies?
um just when they going to snap the
ball, getting a good timing or how the
snap count and how they're going to uh
and when he's about to snap it. Um I
think we had a good game plan on that
and we went out there and executed it
well. So,
>> can you take us through both that that
third first third down that you forced
the incompletion early those two plays?
>> I mean, you know, like I said, man, I
just made the plays that come to me.
It's nothing crazy. I'm not going out my
way to do anything special or nothing
like that. Um we had to play card and I
go out there and do my assignment out
there. So,
>> feel different than any other football.
Uh, nah, not really, man. Like I said,
all year, you know, we treat every game
the same. It really don't feel like we
won the Super Bowl right now. Um, it
seems like we gonna get ready to get
prepared for another game next week. Um,
but you know, like I said, I'm just
ready to celebrate with my guys, man. We
we put a lot of work into this season
and we got to go out there and
celebrate. So,
>> Oh, yeah. I'm going to watch the game. I
don't know when we going to watch it,
but we got to watch it, though.
[laughter]
>> Is the NFC showing that it's the best
conference? It's two years in a row and
pretty resounding victory.
>> No, I don't know, man. Like I said, I'm
just I'm just focus on what we doing
over here in Seattle. So,
>> last question.
>> Um, no, we knew back at OTAAS, like I
said, man, we kind of picked up the
second half of the season last year. We
kind of knew what we was building to and
what we could be able to do. Um, and we
got all our pieces this year, like I
said, we set a standard for ourselves
back at OTAAS. You talking about a group
of guys who look each other now and hold
each other to that standard. That's us
right there. Um, and that defines the
dark side. So,
>> thanks guys.
>> Thank you. Have a good day.
do everything I